<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on The Writer&#39;s Daily</title>
    <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on The Writer&#39;s Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#25 - Cold Showers</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-25-cold-showers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-25-cold-showers/</guid>
      <description>the_question &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s your favourite season?&amp;rdquo;
 Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re a summer slut. You like the coldness of winter. I generally like the season that I&amp;rsquo;m not in. If it&amp;rsquo;s too hot, I freak out. If it&amp;rsquo;s too cold, I freak out as well  the_topic Cold Showers
 I consistently have cold showers everyday. (I won&amp;rsquo;t have it if I&amp;rsquo;m sick) It&amp;rsquo;s just as unbearable each time. It teaches you about dealing with difficult situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#24 - Programming</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-24-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-24-programming/</guid>
      <description>the_question &amp;ldquo;Who do you want to kill?&amp;rdquo;
 Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re a non-violent person. An NPC, perhaps. Maybe sometimes you feel like killing your family. In my case, my family have already killed me personally on the inside, so there&amp;rsquo;s little point in my continuing. Asians are obviously a good submissive target if you want an easy headshot. I personally want to kill wildlife in Africa. No better feeling than shooting an Elephant and watching it fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#23 - Dating</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-23-dating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-23-dating/</guid>
      <description>the_question &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s the most beautiful thing you&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen?&amp;rdquo;
 Maybe you were out travelling and you saw a beautiful sunset. Perhaps it was a food item. The perfect bowl of ramen. Maybe it was a body part because you&amp;rsquo;re a sexual deviant of sorts. In my case, it&amp;rsquo;s of course my current partner, as opposed to previous partners  the_topic Dating
 I probably dated for two years. I absolutely hated dating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#22 - Paleo Diet</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-22-paleo-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-22-paleo-diet/</guid>
      <description>the_question &amp;ldquo;What do you like to drink?&amp;rdquo;
 Are you a raving alcoholic? Addicted to the drink. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re one of those rebel diabetics, smashing the 7-up as the insulin pours out of your ears. I personally like to drink the blood of my victims. Mostly children and cute Chinese squirels. Actually I&amp;rsquo;m pretty boring. I&amp;rsquo;m definitely a water kind of guy.  the_topic Paleo Diet
 I&amp;rsquo;m a pretty health conscious kind of guy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#21 - Drug Dealers</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-21-drug-dealers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-21-drug-dealers/</guid>
      <description>the_question &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s the most selfish thing you&amp;rsquo;ve ever done?&amp;rdquo;
 Maybe you like you hog the TV remote? No sharing candy around the office Maybe you won&amp;rsquo;t let me sleep with your wife I&amp;rsquo;m pretty selfish when it comes to my time. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of time, so anything I can do. I also like to hoard children.  the_topic Drug Dealers
 Just a disclaimer, I&amp;rsquo;ve never been a drug dealer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#20 - Handwriting</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-20-handwriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-20-handwriting/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What website do you use most? The Topic: I talk about my love for handwriting. The Viewermail: .  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#20 - Handwriting</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-20-handwriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-20-handwriting/</guid>
      <description>the_question What website do you use most?
 Are you a facebook person? Maybe Google is the website that you use most. I know reddit is particularly prominent for a lot of people. Send in your websites, on le email. For me it&amp;rsquo;s actually hivandsingle.com  the_topic Handwriting
 Growing up I had really bad handwriting. (attritious) It was like if you ate alphabet spaghetti and then vomitted everywhere. Then I was like 20 I decided that I was going to learn it from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#19 - Estrangement</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-19-estrangement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-19-estrangement/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What do you enjoy most about your day? The Topic: Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about estrangement. The Viewermail: I help feed some hungry people.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#19 - Estrangement</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-19-estrangement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-19-estrangement/</guid>
      <description>the_question What do you enjoy most about your day?
 Maybe you enjoy that morning coffee, along with a hand-rolled cigarette. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just doing what it is that you love doing? Playing video games, working. For me it&amp;rsquo;s just the process of seeing myself grow and progress. Weight lifting and just pushing myself. To see that I&amp;rsquo;m just a bit further along with my life than I was before. It helps create a sense of hope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#18 - Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-18-bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-18-bitcoin/</guid>
      <description> The Question: How long do you plan to work for? The Topic: The highs and lows of the bitcoin flow. The Viewermail: I&amp;rsquo;m a man obsessed with violence.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#18 - Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-18-bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-18-bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>the_question How long do you plan to work for?
 When do you hope to retire? Maybe you think you&amp;rsquo;ll never retire at all. Perhaps you just have no savings. Maybe you have a hard date, like when you&amp;rsquo;re 65. In my case, I want to still remain employed at my current company. I&amp;rsquo;ll Realistically, the best retirement plan is marry a nice rich Jewish girl. (as my mother has literally told me verbatim)  the_topic Bitcoin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#17 - Standing Desk</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-17-standing-desk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-17-standing-desk/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What are you having for dinner tonight! The Topic: I stand at thy desk. The Viewermail: The nun wants to become a slut.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#17 - Standing Desk</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-17-standing-desk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-17-standing-desk/</guid>
      <description>the_question What are you having for dinner tonight!
 Are you a lonely single mother who anticipates eating a frozen TV dinner meal, while your cat walks all over you and leaves nothing but hair and shame across the facade of your fringe? (if so, give me a call, we should hook up!) With all the fasting I generally only eat dinner, so it&amp;rsquo;s like the highlight of my day. If you have a partner or A SLAVE, do they cook for you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#16 - Tekken</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-16-tekken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-16-tekken/</guid>
      <description> The Question: How do you deal with stress? The Topic: The game that got me into fighters. The Viewermail: I help an asexual man out because I&amp;rsquo;m just a good guy.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#16 - Tekken</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-16-tekken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-16-tekken/</guid>
      <description>the_question How do you deal with stress?
 Maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t deal with it at all. (screaming into a pillow) Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re one of those hot Yoga teachers (calm and zen) Personally I like to punch children. For me it&amp;rsquo;s about being pro-active with my mental health.  the_topic Tekken
 I started playing Tekken 7 earlier in 2020. It&amp;rsquo;s the first serious fighting game that I&amp;rsquo;ve played which actually clicked for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#15 - High School</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-15-high-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-15-high-school/</guid>
      <description> The Question: How much time do you spend on social media each day? The Topic: I hated high school like you cannot imagine. The Viewermail: Touched by God.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#15 - High School</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-15-high-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-15-high-school/</guid>
      <description>the_question How much time do you spend on social media each day?
 Are you just obsessed with Instagram, Twitter, Facebook etc. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re like me where you have social media, but you just unfollow everyone and you just chat to people? I like to use social media as like a news platform. Especially Reddit. But I would say I&amp;rsquo;m average. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;d like to spend less time on social media?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#14 - Journalism</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-14-journalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-14-journalism/</guid>
      <description> The Question: How do you contribute towards society? The Topic: The call of the journalist. The Viewermail: Dealing with awful acnee.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#14 - Journalism</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-14-journalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-14-journalism/</guid>
      <description>the_question How do you contribute towards society?
 Do you volunteer at the home shelter? Offering sexual favors to the homeless? Maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t do anything at all. I pay taxes and I help companies grow and I guess that&amp;rsquo;s how I quantify my contribution towards society. I also rape and murder. It&amp;rsquo;s good to give the police a reason to exist, AMIRITE!?!?  the_topic Journalism
 I&amp;rsquo;m a Journalism graduate from Monash uninversity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#13 - Weed</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-13-weed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-13-weed/</guid>
      <description> The Question: Do you feel safe?. The Topic: I promise I&amp;rsquo;m not stoned. The Viewermail: Too much sand?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#13 - Weed</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-13-weed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-13-weed/</guid>
      <description>the_question Do you feel safe?
 Important question to think about. Safety is foundational for humans. I feel incredibly safe. Physically. Emotionally. Slightly worried about job security, as well as the future.  the_topic Weed
 I remember I 1st smoked weed when I was 18 or 19. Then it progressively became a habit and throughout uni, I was getting blazed pretty often. For like the 1st year of uni it was like, once a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#12 - Podcasting</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-12-podcasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-12-podcasting/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What worries you most about the future? The Topic: I am a podcaster, apparently. The Viewermail: Sushi. Sushi. Sushi.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#12 - Podcasting</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-12-podcasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-12-podcasting/</guid>
      <description>the_question What worries you most about the future?
 Does everything make you worried? Does nothing make you worried? Are you one of those anxiety queens? As a stubborn male, very little worries me. I often just don&amp;rsquo;t care and I assume nothing bad will happen or come of it.  the_topic Podcasting
 I thought I&amp;rsquo;d talk about my relationship with podcasting. I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing podcasting and radio since I was 16.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#11 - Productivity</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-11-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-11-productivity/</guid>
      <description> The Question: How much do you care about money?. The Topic: Becoming way too obsessed with productivity. The Viewermail: A listener wants to blow me.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#11 - Productivity</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-11-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-11-productivity/</guid>
      <description>the_question How much do you care about money?
 Are you one of those hardcore capitalists? Where you dream of decapitating socialists by the mouthful. In my case, I would say I care about money more than the average person. I have a mortgage and I am firmly entrenched in the rat race. Plus, money is sexy. You tried masturbating with a dollar bill? It&amp;rsquo;s delicious.  the_topic Productivity
 I used to be obsessed with productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#10 - Gold Stars</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-10-gold-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-10-gold-stars/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What are you worth? The Topic: Gold stars are apparently a bit like masturbation. The Viewermail: Dealing with a nasty divorce. thewritersdailypodcast@gmail.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#10 - Gold Stars</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-10-gold-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-10-gold-stars/</guid>
      <description>the_question What are you worth?
 Would you consider your worth in dollar amounts, what is your price? Maybe you think your life is priceless, or for example would you throw it away to protect those you love? How about in a slave scenario? Personally I can say that I&amp;rsquo;m literally worth nothing, as proved by the lack of tips on my online adult webcam account.  the_topic Gold Stars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#9 - Breakfast</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-9-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-9-breakfast/</guid>
      <description> The Question: When was the last time you treated yourself? The Topic: What&amp;rsquo;s the deal with Breakfast? The Viewermail: It looks like a fan has developed Reade fever. thewritersdailypodcast@gmail.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#9 - Breakfast</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-9-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-9-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>the_question When was the last time you treated yourself?
 If it was moments ago to a dirty wank on the homepage of PornHub then shame on you. In my case, I very rarely treat myself. Usually my partner does it for me. She buys all sorts of nice  the_topic What&amp;rsquo;s the deal with Breakfast?
 I don&amp;rsquo;t eat breakfast I do the whole fasting thing (talk about benefits) The body simply adjusts Probably largely has to do with having more time (a sad facet of modern society)  the_viewermail Jim Jekins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#8 - Monogamy</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-8-monogamy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-8-monogamy/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What do you do really well? The Topic: Stayin&amp;rsquo; with da one gal. The Viewermail: I help a woman conceive.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#8 - Monogamy</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-8-monogamy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-8-monogamy/</guid>
      <description>the_question What do you do really well?
 I give great handjobs. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re really talented at the piano or you&amp;rsquo;re really good at art. Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;re just  the_topic Today we&amp;rsquo;re talking about Spotify (or music streaming)
 It sort of just happened. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember music before streaming. I do remember being very skeptical about it at first.  the_viewermail Mira from Khon Kaen, Thailand
&amp;ldquo;Hey Julius, lovin&amp;rsquo; the show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#7 - Spotify</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-7-spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-7-spotify/</guid>
      <description> The Question: When was the last time you called your mother? The Topic: Music streaming becomes us all. The Viewermail: Overcoming bitchitis.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#7 - Spotify</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-7-spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-7-spotify/</guid>
      <description>the_question When was the last time you calld your mother?
 In my case, I don&amp;rsquo;t speak to my mother anymore. (cold hard bitch) But if you love your mum, give her a call. Dad too. (In my case, I don&amp;rsquo;t even know if he&amp;rsquo;s alive or not) [play fail sound]  the_topic Spotify.
 Talk about music streaming, how it&amp;rsquo;s become a thing. Talk about the old days of pirating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#6 - Centrelink</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-6-centrelink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-6-centrelink/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What can&amp;rsquo;t you live without? The Topic: Makin&amp;rsquo; bank with Centrelink. The Viewermail: The guy has a small penis.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#6 - Centrelink</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-6-centrelink/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-6-centrelink/</guid>
      <description>the_question What&amp;rsquo;s one thing that you can&amp;rsquo;t live without?
 For me it&amp;rsquo;s meth. (actual) I can&amp;rsquo;t live without my mental health. The correct is my partner. (it means she&amp;rsquo;ll blow me tonight)  the_topic Centrelink.
 Explain what Centrelink is Talk about being at a Centrelink Talk about how you were on Centrelink and mum took the money Talk about how it helped bitcoin debt  the_viewermail Ben from Brisbane Australia (Brisvegas)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#5 - Work</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-5-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-5-work/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What is the most important thing in your life? The Topic: Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about work. The Viewermail: Stage four cancer.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#5 - Work</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-5-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-5-work/</guid>
      <description>the_intro the_question What is the most important thing in your life?
 It can maybe be right now, or in the future Maybe you can&amp;rsquo;t answer this question For me it&amp;rsquo;s my future children  the_topic Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about work.
 I&amp;rsquo;m a professional programmer. Work progressively gets easier throughout your career. You Startout doing shit jobs. What are your thoughts about work?  the_viewermail Portia from Barcelona Spain
&amp;ldquo;Hey Julius, huge fan of the daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#4 - Food Delivery</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-4-food-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-4-food-delivery/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What makes you happy? The Topic: Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about food delivery services. The Viewermail: What&amp;rsquo;s the deal with beef?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#4 - Food Delivery</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-4-food-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-4-food-delivery/</guid>
      <description>the_intro the_question What makes you happy?
 What is happiness? I would say there are two kinds to consider: Conditional and unconditional Being mentally balanced makes me happy  the_topic Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about food delivery.
 I don&amp;rsquo;t get it. (nothing wrong with it) I think it comes down to lifestyle. Expensive. $10 is expensive. Hell, $5 is expensive. I like a cooked meal. I also don&amp;rsquo;t mind doing chores.  the_viewermail Elena from Casa de piedra in argentina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#3 - Greyhound</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-3-greyhound/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-3-greyhound/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What excites you in life? The Topic: Adopting a greyhound. The Viewermail: Ying Ying wants a visa.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#3 - Greyhound</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-3-greyhound/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-3-greyhound/</guid>
      <description>the_intro the_question What excites you in life?
 Maybe nothing excites you Pushing myself excites me Opportunity excites me  the_topic Talk about how I adopted a Greyhound.
 It&amp;rsquo;s 100% worth it. It&amp;rsquo;s a commitment. Improved my mental health Prepared me for having children  the_viewermail Ying Ying from the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China.
&amp;ldquo;Julius, I absolutely love the show. I think it&amp;rsquo;s fantastic! I&amp;rsquo;m currently looking to live in Australia, but unfortunately it&amp;rsquo;s almost impossible to get a visa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#2 - Quarantine</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-2-quarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-2-quarantine/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What do you do for your mental health everyday? The Topic: Getting through quarantine. The Viewermail: How to get your dad to stop beating you.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#2 - Quarantine</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-2-quarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-2-quarantine/</guid>
      <description>the_intro the_question What do you do for your mental health everyday?
 I&amp;rsquo;m bipolar and balance is the name of my game. I meditate. Cold showers, I lift everyday.  the_topic How are you getting through quarantine?
 Loving it. Absolutely Loving it. Working from home benefits (saving on commute etc.) I&amp;rsquo;m very routine focused.  the_viewermail Timmy from Kansas City, Misouri.
&amp;ldquo;Hey Julius, loving the crop top. My question to you today is, my dad is an alcoholic keeps beating me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 - Beginning</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-1-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/episodes/ep-1-beginning/</guid>
      <description> The Question: What do you want to achieve today? The Topic: The very first show The Viewermail: The guy has a foot fetish.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 - Beginning</title>
      <link>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-1-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 07:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thewritersdaily.juliusreade.com/epn/ep-1-beginning/</guid>
      <description>the_intro the_question What do you want to achieve today?
 What&amp;rsquo;s your priority? In my case it&amp;rsquo;s recording the show. And not crying. That&amp;rsquo;s not true. Men don&amp;rsquo;t cry, we just masturbate vigorously until we pass out.   the_topic What is this show about?
 Want to have fun Comedy/Motivational Podcast I want it to make you feel Marketing platform for my novel  the_viewermail Julius Reade from Melbourne, Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>